Guide to the Transport Workers Union of America: Records of Locals WAG.234
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Records of TWU Local 100 (New York City), 1931-1978.
  - Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1956-1959 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - American Irish National Immigrant Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - American Labor Party, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - American Labor Party, 1940, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - American Labor Party, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - American Legion, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - American Polish Labor Council, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - American Red Cross, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - American Red Cross, 1953-1958 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Americans for Democratic, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - American Transport Union, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - American Transport Union, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Anniversary, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Anti-Union Material, 1937-1941 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Applications for Employment, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Apprentice Training, 1964, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Assaults, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Associated Irish Societies, 1956, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Associated Transit Guild, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Automation, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Automobile Club of America, 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Auxiliary Bus Transport Plan, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Avenue B and East Broadway Transit Co., 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Avenue B and East Broadway Transit Co., 1940-1942 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Avenue B and East Broadway Transit Co., 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Avenue B and East Broadway Transit Co., 1961-1972 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Barnes, Henry (Traffic Commissioner), 1962-1965 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - %"beakies", 1954-1959 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Bee Line, Inc., 1937-1945, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Bee Lines, Rockville Center Bus, Utility Lines Merger, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Belous, Charles, 1949-1952 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Belous, Charles, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Belous, Charles (I), 1955 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Belous, Charles (II), 1955 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Belous, Charles, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Benefits, 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Benefits, 1953-1967 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Benefits: Comparative Data, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Benefits: Deceased Members, 1951, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Benefits: Dental Plan, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Benefits: Optical Plan, 1952-1956 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Benevolent Committee of IRT, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Bernacchia Bros. Inc., 1945 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Berry, Theodore, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Black Workers Council, ca.1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Blood Bank, 1954, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Blue Cross, 1960-1965 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - BMT: General, 1931, 1936-1939 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - BMT: General, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - BMT: General, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - BMT: General, 1948, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - BMT: General, 1952-1957, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_2ee6eadde97dd460173ab00c7931867c)
  - BMT: Car Maintenance, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - BMT: Car Maintenance, 1942, 1948-1963 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - BMT: Station Employees, 1952-1953 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - BMT: Strike Clippings, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Board of Estimate, 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Board of Mediation, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Board of Transportation: General, 1936-1937 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Board of Transportation: General, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Board of Transportation: General, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Board of Transportation: General, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Board of Transportation: General, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Board of Transportation: General (I), 1944 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Board of Transportation: General (II), 1944 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Board of Transportation: General, 1945-1947 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Board of Transportation: General, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Board of Transportation: General, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Board of Transportation: General (1950 I) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Board of Transportation: General (1950 II) (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Board of Transportation: General, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Board of Transportation: General, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Board of Transportation: General, 1953-1956 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Board of Transportation: BMT, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Board of Transportation: BMT, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Board of Transportation: Bingham, Sidney, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Board of Transportation: Bingham, Sidney, 1951, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Board of Transportation: Clerical Force, 1952-1953 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Board of Transportation: Commissioners, 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Board of Transportation: Daily, W.J., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Board of Transportation: Daily, W.J., 1951 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Board of Transportation: Daily, W.J, 1952-1953 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Board of Transportation: Demonstration, Jun 1951 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Board of Transportation: Dispute, Jan 1942-Oct 1942 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Board of Transportation: Dispute, Nov 1942-Dec 1942 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Board of Transportation: Economy drive, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Board of Transportation Impartial Grievance Committee, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Board of Transportation: IND, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Board of Transportation: IND, 1943, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Board of Transportation: IRT, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Board of Transportation: IRT, 1943, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Board of Transportation: Joint Report of Engineers, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Board of Transportation: News, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Board of Transportation: Organizing, 1952-1953 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Board of Transportation: Petitions, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Board of Transportation Publications, 1943, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Board of Transportation: Report, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Board of Transportation: Seniority, 1939-1952 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Board of Transportation: Sick Leave, 1947-1952 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Board of Transportation: Sullivan, Frank, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Board of Transportation: Trials (IRT), 1940 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Board of Transportation: Vacations, 1947-1952 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Board of Transportation: Woods, John, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Board of Transportation: Working Conditions, General, 1946-1950 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Bond Issue, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Book Keeper, Stenographers and Accountants (UOPWA), 1939 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Borough President, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - British Trade Unions, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Brooklyn Battery Tunnel, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Brooklyn Conference, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Brooklyn Office, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Brooklyn Transit Cuts (I), 1954 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Brooklyn Transit Cuts (II), 1954 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Brooklyn Transit Cuts, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Brooklyn Transit Cuts, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Brotherhood of IRT Company Employees, 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Brotherhood of IRT Company: Petitions, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1951-1954 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Brotherhood Party, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Building, 1949-1956 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Building, 1964-1967 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Building and Allied Trades Council, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Bulletin (Executive Committee Local 100), 1956-1966 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Burnell, John, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Bus Lines: General, 1950-1953 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Bus Lines: General, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Bus Lines: General, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Bus Lines, Sale of, 1954-1960 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Bus Maintenance Division, 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Bus Operators: Illness, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Bus Riders: Decline, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Bus Strike (I), 1941 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Bus Strike (II), 1941 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Bus Strike, Jun 1949-Aug 1949 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Bus Strike, 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Bus Strike, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Bus Strike: Clippings, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Bus Strike: Clippings, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Bus Strike: Clippings, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Bus Strike: Clippings, Jun 1949-Aug 1949 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Bus Strike: Clippings, Nov 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Bus Strike: Clippings, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Bus Strike: Clippings, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Bus Strike: Clippings, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Bus Strike: Contributors, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Bus Strike: Correspondence, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Bus Strike: Correspondence, Jun 1949-Aug 1949 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Bus Strike: Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Bus Strike: Correspondence, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Bus Strike: Correspondence, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Bus Strike: Telegrams, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Bus Strike (Wildcat), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Bus Strike (Wildcat) Blumenauer, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Bus Strike (Wildcat): Clippings, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Bus Strike (Wildcat): Hearings, pp 1-62, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Bus Strike (Wildcat): Hearings, pp 1-286 a, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Bus Strike (Wildcat): pp 287-415 a, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Bus Strike (Wildcat): pp 416-630 a, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Bus Strike (Wildcat): Hearings, pp 631-691, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Bus Strike (Wildcat): Hearings, pp 692-867, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Bus Strike (Wildcat): Hearings, pp 868-1079, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Bus Strike (Wildcat): Hearings, pp 1080-1290 a, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Bus Strike (Wildcat): Hynes Suspension, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - By-Laws, undated, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - By-Laws, 1953, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Car Equipment Economics, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Carey Transportation Co., 1949 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Car Maintenance Dept., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Car Maintenance Dept., 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Car Maintenance Dept., 1960-1964 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Car Maintenance Dept., 1965-1970 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Car Maintenance Dept., 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Car Maintenance Dept: Human Relations Committee, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Chairmen (Transit Authority), 1954-1956 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Change Booths: Petition, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Change of Title, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Charter Members, ca.1964 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Check-Off, 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Check-Off, 1955, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Check-Off Revocations, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Chief Engineers Department, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Children's Bus Service, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Church and Work Congress, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - CIO, 1938-1952 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - CIO, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - CIO:NY State Industrial Union Council, 1938-1940 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - CIO-PAC, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - CIO-PAC, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Citizen's Transit Committee, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Citizen's Transit Committee, 1943, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Citizenship, 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Civil Defense, 1941, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Civil Service, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Civil Service, 1948-1951 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Civil Service, 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Civil Service, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Civil Service: Blumberg, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Civil Service Bulletin, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1952-1958 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1940, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Civil Service Commission:Reclassification, BMT, IRT, Jan 1941-Apr 1941 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Civil Service Commission: Reclassification Resolutions, BMT, IRT, May 1941-Dec 1941 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Civil Service Form, 1954-1956 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Civil Service Information Bulletin (TWU), 1940 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Civil Service: Questionnaires, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Civil Service Reports Weekly, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Classes (TWU), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Clerical News, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Clerical Staff, 1953-1955 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Clerical Workers: Transit Authority, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Collective Bargaining Units: Report, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Commerce and Industry Association, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Committee for a United Ireland, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Committee for Better Transit, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Committee for trade Unity, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Committee to Encourage Riding, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Committee to End the Ban on Negroes in Organized Baseball, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Committee to Upgrade Station Department, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Communist Party, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Community Services Committee, 1959-1961 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Complaints, 1940-1948 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Complaints, 1953-1955 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Complaints, 1956-1958 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Complaints, 1959-1963 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Complaints, 1964-1970 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Conductor, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Conductor-Towermen Division, 1962-1969 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Conductor's Benevolent Association, 1956-1958 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Conductors: Elimination of, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Connolly Commemoration, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Constitution, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Contract, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Contract Expiration Dates, 1962-1965 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Contract Fund, 1959-1962 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Contract Proposals, 1938-1939 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Convention (TWU), 1950 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Convention (TWU), 1955 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Convention (TWU), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Convention (TWU), 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Convention (TWU), 1965 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Contributions, 1953-1955 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Contributions, 1959-1961 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Contributions, 1962-1964 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Controller (NYC), 1953 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Convention, 1937-1939 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Convention, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Convention, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Convention, 1952-1955 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Convention, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - COPE, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - COPE, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - COPE, 1966-1970 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Cost of Living Clauses (Report), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Council of Better Transit Organizations, ca.1969-1970, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Credit Unions, 1939-1943 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Council for Peace and Civil Liberties, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Crime in the Subways, 1963, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Death Benefit, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Deborah Hospital, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Delegations, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Dept. of Welfare, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Diesel Fuel Tax Bill, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Differential Day, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Disability Insurance, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Disorderly Conduct, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Disqualified Men, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Dissidents, General, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Division Officers, 1960- [1964] (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Donations, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Donations, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Donations, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Donations, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Donations, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Draggin' the Line, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Dues, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Dues, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Dues, 1949, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Dues, 1955-1962 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Dues Analysis, 1941-1942 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Dues Analysis, 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Dues Analysis, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Dues Analysis, 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Dress and Initiation Letters, 1954-1956 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Dues Increase, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Dues Increase, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Easter Week Commemoration, 1967-1971 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - East Side and Comprehensive Omnibus Corp., 1937-1938 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - East Side and Comprehensive Omnibus Corp., 1939 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - East Side and Comprehensive Omnibus Corp., 1941-1942 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - East Side and Comprehensive Omnibus Corp., 1943 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - East Side and Comprehensive Omnibus Corp., 1944 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - East Side and Comprehensive Omnibus Corp., 1945 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - East Side and Comprehensive Omnibus Corp: Wages, 1941, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Economic Reports, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Education, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Educational Committee, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Educational Committee, undated, 1950-1954 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Educational Department, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Educational Department, 1940-1941 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Educational Director, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Educational Director, 1938-1939 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - EL: Demolition, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - EL: Demolition, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - EL: Demolition, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - EL: Demolition, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - EL: Demolition, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - EL: Sixth Ave., 1938-1939 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Election (Executive Board BMT): Petitions: Peter Ezzo, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Election (Executive Board BMT): Petitions: Frank Doherty, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Election (Executive Board BMT): Petitions: Leo Miller, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Election (Executive Board BMT): Petitions: John Pachter, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Election (Executive Board IND): Petitions: Angelo Androzzi, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Election (Executive Board Third Ave.): Petitions: Michael Fitzgibbon, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Election (Executive Board Third Ave.): Petitions: William Valentine, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Election (Executive Board Third Ave.): Petitions: Gilbert Weisberger, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Election (Executive Board IRT): Petitions: James Gahagan, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Election (Executive Board IRT): Petitions: Julius DeLuca, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Election (Executive Board IRT): Petitions: Buster Giordano, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Election (Executive Board IRT): Petitions: Thomas King, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Election (Executive Board IRT): Petitions: Patrick McCarthy, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Election (Executive Board IRT): Petitions: Frank Moon, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Election (Executive Board IRT): Petitions: Paul Muschalik, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Election (Executive Board IRT): Petitions: Frank O'Connor, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Election (Executive Board IRT): Petitions: Nora O'Grady, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Election (Executive Board IRT):Petitions: James Quinn, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Election (Executive Board IRT): Petitions: Gerald O'Reilly, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Election (Executive Board IRT): Petitions: John O'Sullivan, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Election (Executive Board IRT): Petitions: Ellis Van Riper, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Election (Executive Board IRT President): Petitions: Austin Hogan, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Election (Recording Secretary): Petitions: John Leary, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Election (Secretary-Treasurer): Petitions: Joseph Celenza, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Election (Secretary-Treasurer): Petitions: Gustav Faber, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Election (Second Vice-President): Petitions: Matthew Guinan, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Election (Third Vice-President): Petitions: John Hamilton, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Elections, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Elections, 1935 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Elections, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Elections, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Elections, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Elections, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Elections, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Elections, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Elections, 1943-1946 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Elections, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Elections, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Elections, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Elections, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Elections, 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Elections, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Elections, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Elections, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Elections, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Elections, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Elections, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Elections, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Elections, 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Elections, 1970-1973 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Elections: Organizers, 1948, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Elections: Protest, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Elections: Ratification, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Elections: Representation, 1957, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Elections: Sections, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Elections: Sections, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Electrical Powermens Association, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Employees' Facilities Rehabilitation Program, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Employees' Facilities Rehabilitation Program, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Employment Requests, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Employment Requests, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Employment Requests, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Employment Requests, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Employment Requests, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Employment Requests, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Employment Requests, 1961-1970 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Enlarged Joint Executive Committee, 1942, 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Enlarged Joint Executive Committee, 1954-1957 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Enlarged Joint Executive Committee, 1958-1961 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Enlarged Joint Executive Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Enlarged Joint Executive Committee, 1964-1970 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Exact Fare, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board, 1937-1939, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board, 1944-1950 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board, 1951-1952 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board, 1953-1954 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board, 1955-1957 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board, 1961-1973 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board: Attendance, 1946-1947 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board: Notices, 1942-1949 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee, 1950-1953 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Fact Finding Board: General, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Fact Finding Board, Feb 6, 1950-Feb 8, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Fact Finding Board (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Fact Finding Board (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Fact Finding Board, Mar 7, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Fact Finding Board, Mar 28, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Fact Finding Board, Apr 12, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Fact Finding Board, Apr 13, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Fact Finding Board, Apr 14, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Fact Finding Committee, Jun 2, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Fact Finding Committee (I), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 2)